Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]s
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]s
[Between Love and Frost]
[بين الحب والصقيع]
[Episode 2]
[الحلقة الثانية]
You don't remember me, sir?
ألا تتذكرني يا سيدي؟
Ten years ago,
منذ عشر سنوات،
it was you who celebrated my birthday.
لقد كنت أنت الذي احتفل بعيد ميلادي.
How was there a survivor?
كيف كان هناك ناجي؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
What do I want?
ماذا أريد؟
Murder
قتل
demands a life in return.
يُطالب بحياة في المقابل.
But I'm willing to give you
ولكنني على استعداد لإعطائك
a chance.
فرصة.
The keys to the chains
مفاتيح السلاسل
are sewn into each other's stomachs.
يتم خياطتهم في بطون بعضهم البعض.
Retrieve the keys,
استرجاع المفاتيح
and maybe you'll live.
وربما ستعيش.
I shall excuse myself.
سأعتذر عن نفسي.
Don't go!
لا تذهب!
Sun,
شمس،
you want to kill me?
هل تريد قتلي؟
I don't want to die here.
لا أريد أن أموت هنا.
[In memory of Chu family]
[في ذكرى عائلة تشو]
[Palace of Joy]
[قصر الفرح]
The next deal
الصفقة القادمة
is to kill him.
هو قتله.
You'd kill your brother?
هل ستقتل أخاك؟
He's not my biological brother.
إنه ليس أخي البيولوجي.
I'm not connected to them.
أنا لست مرتبطًا بهم.
I'm only the Gu family's adopted son.
أنا فقط الابن المتبنى لعائلة جو.
He's got the evidence.
لقد حصل على الدليل.
I can't let him live.
لا أستطيع أن أتركه يعيش.
I'll handle it as you wish.
سأتعامل مع الأمر كما تريد.
In return, I want Chu Huaixuan captured alive.
في المقابل، أريد القبض على تشو هوايشوان حيًا.
This guy wants to kill his brother.
هذا الرجل يريد قتل أخيه.
Why didn't he tell us yesterday?
لماذا لم يخبرنا بالأمس؟
If Gu Tongpei wakes up and runs back to his mansion,
إذا استيقظ Gu Tongpei وركض عائداً إلى قصره،
it'll be hard for us to act.
سيكون من الصعب علينا التصرف.
Stop jinxing it.
توقف عن التسبب في النحس.
Nobody.
لا أحد.
I really called it!
لقد اتصلت به حقا!
You jinxed it.
لقد جلبت له النحس.
He must've heard us
لا بد أنه سمعنا
and escaped through the window.
وهرب من النافذة.
Hurry and block him.
اسرع و قم بحظره.
I'll ask our men to go to the Governor's Mansion.
سأطلب من رجالنا أن يذهبوا إلى قصر الحاكم.
- Yes.
- نعم.
You stole my thing,
لقد سرقت شيئى
and now you're back.
والآن عدت.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I...
أنا...
missed you.
لقد افتقدتك.
Give it back to me.
أعدها لي.
What?
ماذا؟
I have no idea. Search me.
ليس لدي أي فكرة. ابحث عني.
Take off your clothes.
اخلع ملابسك.
Don't take risks.
لا تخاطر.
I may consider
قد أفكر
letting you live.
السماح لك بالعيش.
Don't break my stuff.
لا تكسر أغراضي.
Give it back!
أعيدها!
Seems this watch
يبدو أن هذه الساعة
means a lot to you.
يعني الكثير بالنسبة لك.
I'm keeping it.
انا احتفظ به.
Tomorrow afternoon,
غدا بعد الظهر
bring my thing
أحضر لي الشيء
to the warehouse in the eastern suburbs
إلى المستودع في الضواحي الشرقية
to exchange with me.
للتبادل معي.
Remember,
يتذكر،
come alone.
تعال وحدك.
Beauties really like to be late.
الجميلات يحبون حقا أن يتأخرن.
I just wanted to have a talk.
أردت فقط أن أتحدث.
We have no grudges.
ليس لدينا ضغائن.
Why do you want to kill me?
لماذا تريد قتلي؟
Sorry,
آسف،
I don't like chatting with unknown men.
لا أحب الدردشة مع الرجال المجهولين.
Stay still.
ابقى ساكنا.
Drop the gun.
أسقط البندقية.
Kick it away.
اركله بعيدا.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Demand anything you want.
اطلب أي شيء تريده.
Demand?
يطلب؟
Take off your clothes and throw them to me.
اخلع ملابسك وألقيها لي.
Maybe I'll let you live.
ربما سأدعك تعيش.
Are you getting back at me?
هل تريد الانتقام مني؟
Do it.
افعلها.
Throw away those strange things
تخلص من تلك الأشياء الغريبة
on you.
عليك.
Go on.
إستمر.
I've got no weapons left.
لم يعد لدي أي أسلحة.
How will I know without checking?
كيف سأعرف دون التحقق؟
Never expected you were like this.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن تكون هكذا.
You want me to take my pants off too, do you?
هل تريد مني أن أخلع بنطالي أيضًا ؟
Hey.
يا.
If men talk too much,
إذا تحدث الرجال كثيرا،
they are not attractive.
إنهم ليسوا جذابين.
[Keep Quiet] This is absurd.
[ابقى هادئًا] هذا سخيف.
Looks like they got robbed
يبدو أنهم تعرضوا للسرقة
at the eastern post station.
في محطة البريد الشرقية.
Even their clothes were stripped off.
حتى تم نزع ملابسهم.
Serves them right.
يستحقون ذلك.
No decent person would go there.
لن يذهب هناك أي شخص محترم.
[Cunji Hospital of Jiang City]
[مستشفى كونجي بمدينة جيانغ]
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
[Palace of Joy]
[قصر الفرح]
Looks like things didn't go smoothly.
يبدو أن الأمور لم تسير بسلاسة.
You didn't tell me
لم تخبرني
your brother was so dangerous.
لقد كان أخوك خطيرًا جدًا.
Your target is
هدفك هو
the richest man in the city.
أغنى رجل في المدينة.
Mine is the Young Marshal of Gu family.
أنا المارشال الشاب لعائلة جو.
Neither of them is an easy one.
لا يعتبر أي منهما سهلاً.
The issue is I've been compromised.
المشكلة هي أنني تعرضت للخطر.
It's hard to approach him again.
من الصعب الاقتراب منه مرة أخرى.
You can't give up.
لا يمكنك الاستسلام.
You must find a way.
يجب عليك أن تجد طريقة.
Mr. Gu, good evening.
السيد جو، مساء الخير.
Master and Young Master are waiting for you for dinner.
المعلم والمعلم الشاب في انتظاركم لتناول العشاء.
Die,
ال،
have the kitchen make some stir-fried kidneys.
اطلب من المطبخ أن يصنع بعض الكلى المقلية.
I need the nourishment.
أحتاج إلى الغذاء.
Sure, I'll see to it.
بالتأكيد، سأرى ذلك.
Pei.
يحب.
Father?
أب؟
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
good timing.
توقيت جيد.
Let me introduce
دعني أقدم لك
my girlfriend to you,
صديقتي لك
Chu Minghui.
تشو مينغوي.
Minghui,
مينغهوي،
this is Gu Tongpei, my younger brother.
هذا هو جو تونغبي، أخي الأصغر.
Glad to meet you, Tongpei.
يسعدني أن ألتقي بك، تونغبي.
Likewise, Minghui.
وبالمثل، مينغوي.
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
♪الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها♪
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي، زاد خوفي
♪Sparks of hatred ignite within the heart♪
♪تشتعل شرارات الكراهية في القلب♪
♪The more I struggle, the hoarser my voice becomes♪
كلما كافحت أكثر، أصبح صوتي أكثر خشونة
♪I guard myself over and over again♪
♪أحمي نفسي مرارا وتكرارا♪
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
♪أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة♪
♪I feign, struggle♪
♪أتظاهر، أكافح♪
♪Flee, and break♪
♪اهرب وانكسر♪
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
♪قيد الظلام الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪Let the hatred go♪
♪اترك الكراهية تذهب♪
♪Don't dwell♪
♪لا تتوقف♪
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
♪فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتشكل الندوب♪
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
♪دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح♪
♪Let myself be free♪
♪أسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا♪